http://www.paragonslidecabinets.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy PolicyParagon Slide Cabinet Privacy
This statement discloses the privacy practices for both our web site and e-mail system. We have designed Paragon Slide Cabinet so that no personal identifying information is displayed online or is accessible to the general public. We do not reveal your e-mail address and do not ask for your personal information. We do not sell or rent our customer information to any outside party under any circumstances.
If you provide Paragon Slide Cabinet with your e-mail address and you would like to receive information and updates about Paragon Slide Cabinet increased inventory or specials we will keep you informed. Otherwise, Paragon Slide Cabinet will not send you further updates.
We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. When such a change is made, we will post the revised Privacy policy on our website so please bookmark this page and check back periodically. Any changes, corrections or updates to your transactional information can be edited during the purchase process. Questions regarding the Toolfetch.com Privacy Policy should be directed to sales@paragonslidecabinets.com.
Paragon Slide Cabinet Security
Your browser and Paragon Slide Cabinet Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure online commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet.
Paragon Slide Cabinet Cookies
Paragon Slide Cabinet uses third-party persistent cookies to serve you personalized advertising. If you would like to opt-out of receiving this personalized advertising, you can click the following link and those ads will no longer be served to you. Click Here to Opt-Out.
Sign Up For Our Newsletter
